我们天上的主
Our Father, who art in heaven,
愿人都尊你的名为圣
hallowed be Thy name.
愿你的国降临  愿你的旨意
Thy kingdom come, Thy will be done
行在世间如同行在天堂
on Earth as it is in heaven.
赐予我们日用的饮食
Give us this day our daily bread
宽恕我们的罪
and forgive us our trespasses,
如我们宽恕别人一般
as we forgive those who trespass against us,
指引我们避开诱惑
and lead us not into temptation,
带领我们远离罪恶
but deliver us from evil.
阿门
Amen.
欢迎来到女妖镇
镇界 请注意交通安全
看来你今天过的很糟  来杯威士忌吧
I'm gonna go with shitty day and whiskey neat.
你是进镇还是离镇
You coming or going?
我还没想好
I'm still working that out.
这儿一直都这么安静吗
Is it always this quiet around here?
来刺激一下当地经济
Let's stimulate the local economy.
-下一轮酒算我的  -好啊
- Next round's on me. - All right.
你们这些游客今天老给我买酒喝
All you tourists buying me drinks today.
我不是来旅游的  我叫卢卡斯·胡德
Oh, I'm not a tourist. My name's Lucas Hood.
下周一就宣誓就职  就任新警长
Come Monday, I'm being sworn in as the new sheriff.
恭喜你了
Congratulations.
你的头儿知道你在这吗
Your boss know you're here?
不用你操心
Don't you worry about him.
你知道规矩
You know the drill.
看看这家伙
Look at this guy.
不好意思  我们打扰到你了吗
Excuse me. Are we disturbing you?
完全没有  这牛排很好
No, not at all. This is just a very good steak.
我知道自己一站起来对付你们
And I know once I stand up to deal with you fellas,
你们要么会投降  要么会被我宰了
well, maybe you'll come quietly or maybe I'll have to kill you.
但不管怎样  牛排会冷掉的
But either way, this steak is gonna get cold.
虽然可以再热  味道却不一样了
And you can always reheat a steak, but it's never quite the same.
你胆子真不小  狗娘养的
You have some balls on you, motherfucker.
我是警察  放下枪
Sheriff's Department. I'll take that gun now.
你把枪放下
You drop your fucking gun.
你们都把枪放下吧
Why don't you all put your fucking guns down?
现在的局面对谁都不利
See, what we have here is a lose-lose situation.
但是还有别的选择
There's still options on the table.
你们可以放聪明点  拿上点钱
You boys could be smart, take a wad of cash,
再带瓶波本酒
a bottle of bourbon,
回家坐沙发上大喝一顿
go home, sit on the porch, get drunk.
安然度过今天
Call it a good day.
你们也可以犯傻
Or you can be stupid.
跟我们这位警长动枪
Try and shoot it out with the sheriff here.
即便是最好的情况  你们也得死一个
Best-case scenario, one of you boys is dead.
想想吧
Think about that.
我看你也不傻
Seems like a no-brainer to me.
但我看人也不一定准
But then, what the fuck do I know?
拿钱走人  混蛋
Take the money, assholes.
我们拿着钱和酒走人
We'll take the cash and the bourbon.
警长
Sheriff?
谢了
Thanks.
我该请你们再喝一轮了
That deserves another round on me.
抱歉钱被他们拿走了
Sorry about your cash.
没事
Don't mention it.
谢谢你救了我一命
Thanks for saving my ass.
不客气
No problem.
他好像有急事要处理
He seemed to be in an awful hurry.
迈尔斯自助餐厅
我找地方穿个鼻环吧
Maybe I can get my nose pierced somewhere.
想得美
Don't even think about it.
比蒂她妈妈就同意了
Beaty's mom said she could get her nose pierced.
好嘛
Come on.
好不好  爸爸
Come on, Dad.
连车都不想下吗
Couldn't get out of the car,
我不怪你
I don't blame you.
我知道现在一切都很混乱  但是...
I know everything is so messed up, but...
这个镇需要警长  胡德
this town needs a sheriff, Hood.
明白吗
You hear me?
胡德
Hood?
而我需要的
And what I need
是咱俩找到那个混蛋
is for the two of us to go find that fucker
让他为做过的事付出代价
and make him pay for what he did to her.
《黑吃黑》第三季 第六集
Banshee S03E06
一切事物皆有时节
There is a season for everything.
世间一切皆有定时
A time for every event under heaven.
生有时
A time to be born,
死亦有时
a time to die.
种植之时
A time to plant
收获亦有时
and a time to uproot what was planted.
杀戮有时
A time to kill...
医治亦有时
and a time to heal.
拆毁有时
There is a time to tear down
建造建造有时
and a time to build up.
今日  是我们
Today is the time
为我们亲爱的姐妹莉亚的逝世
we mourn our dear sister Leah's passing
及她世间之旅的终结进行缅怀的时刻
and weep for the end of her earthly journey.
而明天则是时候重整旗鼓
And tomorrow will be the time to move on,
为她正直的生活
to celebrate her righteous life
和在天堂获得的救赎而欢欣鼓舞
and revel in Leah's heavenly salvation.
你还好吗
How are you?
凯和莉亚有二十年没说过话了
Kai and Leah didn't speak for 20 years.
我们不想重蹈覆辙
We don't want that.
求求你  回家来吧
Please, come home.
我们原谅你
We forgive you.
我不原谅你们
I don't forgive you.
永远也不会
And I never will.
-别这样  丽贝卡  -再见  母亲
- Please, Rebecca. - Good-bye, Mother.
我们之间的一切  到底哪些是真的
What we had, was any of it real?
都是真的
All of it.
我不想死在今晚
I don't want to die tonight.
别  别
Please. Please.
那时你真的会离开吗
Would you really just have walked away?
如果这是你希望的
If that's what you want.
如果不是呢
What if it isn't?
那我们就一起走
Then we leave together.
要我帮你接吗
You want me to get that?
我只是想来道个别
I just wanted to say good-bye.
谢谢你对我母亲关爱和同情
Thank you for showing such compassion for my mother...
艾米丽
Emily.
我该陪她走完最后一程的
I should have been there to say good-bye.
吗啡影响了她的语言能力
The morphine was affecting her speech,
但我知道  她弥留之际
but I do know that in her final moments
心里想的是你
she was thinking of you.
想她有多爱你
How much she loved you.
有多为你而骄傲
How proud she was.
你的母亲是位坚强而诚实的女人
Your mother was a tough and honest woman.
她看到了你好的一面
She saw the good in you.
我也是
So do I.
你没事吧
You okay?
没事  找我什么事
Yeah, I'm fine. What can I do for you?
我刚刚跟普罗科特的新律师聊了聊
I just went a few rounds with Proctor's new lawyer.
胡德这事  估计会很麻烦
This situation with Hood is gonna be messy.
普罗科特拒捕  还袭警
Proctor resisted arrest and assaulted the sheriff.
这事我看毫无争议
Seems pretty cut and dry to me.
如果这是事实的话
If that's what really happened.
-这就是事实  -很好
- Yeah, that's what really happened. - Good.
你信就好
Glad you believe that
反正出庭作证的是你
since you'll be the one testifying at the trial.
-为什么是我  -你是负责逮捕的警官
- Why me? - You're the arresting officer.
胡德是受害者
Hood was a victim.
我的证人可不是这么说的  布罗克
I've got witnesses that say otherwise, Brock.
这事不会毫无争议  情况很复杂
That's not cut and dry, it's complicated.
这么说吧  戈登
You know what, Gordon?
只要能给凯·普罗科特定罪  让我干嘛都行
I will do anything you need to convict Kai Proctor.
听起来像是私人恩怨
Sounds personal.
本来就是
It is.
介意我来两枪吗
You mind?
不介意  你随意
Yeah, be my guest.
一定要握紧枪把  因为...
Make sure you get a good, firm grip on that handle 'cause it--
你常射击吗
Shoot much?
偶尔吧
Yeah, now and then.
他会没事的  知道吗
He's gonna be okay, you know.
我知道
Oh, I know.
他以前也心碎过不少次
Ain't like he's never had his heart broke before.
但每次的活儿都不一样
But not all jobs are created equal.
这次要是搞砸  我们就死定了
Any fuckups on this one could get us all dead.
所以呢  你要取消吗
So, what, you want to call it off?
我怎么想不重要
Don't matter what I want.
弄完了我和你说
I'll let you know when it's done.
你需要什么
What do you need?
我不喝
Nothing.
宝贝  从1990年开始
Baby, I ain't talked you out of doing something
我就没劝过你
since nineteen-ninety-never,
所以我再问你一次
so I'm going to ask you again.
你需要什么
What do you need?
警官  我们有情况了
Sir, we have a situation.
这个又高又黑的纳粹分子是哪位
Who the hell is tall, dark, and Nazi?
怎么了  邦克
What is it, Bunker?
联邦调查局调了一支战术小队
The FBI has got a TAC team
部署在凯迪店里
setting up shop inside the Cadi.
他们发现了切顿
They found Chayton.
布罗克觉得应该告诉你
Brock figured you'd want to know.
我相信你和我一样对此感到"高兴"
I'm sure you're as happy about this as I am.
谁是负责人
Who's in charge?
没有警徽的人请马上离开
Anybody not wearing a badge clear out now.
你猜
One guess.
胡德  两位能回避下吗
Hood. Can you guys give us a minute?
你是想让我好好配合吗
You want me to play nice?
我想要什么并不重要
It's not what I want that matters.
切顿·里特斯通现在由司法部接手了
Chayton Littlestone is the DOJ's problem now.
指挥权归联邦调查局所有
The feds have operational command.
不要让这件事难上加难了
Don't make this harder than it needs to be.
弗瑞罗指挥官
Commander Ferillo.
这位是警长胡德
This is Sheriff Hood.
他和他的队伍来了  你可以任意调遣
He and his team are here to support you in any way you see fit.
谢谢  镇长先生  你们来得正是时候
Thank you, Mr. Mayor. You're just in time.
我正要给手下说明情况
I was about to brief my men.
我们的首要任务是等级为一级的威胁
Our primary target is a threat level one.
局长已经批准了
Director has authorized
必要时可以使用局长权限的武力
the use of necessary force in his apprehension.
空中侦测在奇诺部落领地内
Eye in the sky has detected
发现了一个地处偏僻的红骨帮营地
a remote Redbone encampment deep in Kinaho territory.
这片地区被密集的树林覆盖  交通不便
The area is heavily wooded with limited vehicle access
营地位置
夜间可视性也有限
and limited nighttime visibility.
重案反应小组会驻扎在这条临近的通路上
CIRG will stage on this adjacent access road.
我们步行靠近
We'll approach on foot.
破晓时分我们就执行逮捕行动
We'll execute the arrest warrant at first light.
-有问题吗  -有  我们呢
- Any questions? - Yeah, what about us?
本地执法人员和奇诺警局的人
Local law enforcement and members of Kinaho PD
将对这次行动进行观察
will observe the operation.
观察
Observe?
警长  我知道这个人杀了你们的人
Sheriff, I know this guy killed one of your own
对此我深感同情
and I am sympathetic to that.
所以才邀请你们同行
That's why you're being invited along.
但是请你清楚
But make no mistake;
这个案子已在联邦管辖范围内
this matter falls under federal jurisdiction.
所以就当帮大家个忙  别参与进来
So, please, do us all a favor and stay out of the way.
当然了
Sure thing.
你能把这张桌子布置一下吗
Can you get this table set up?
能不能把这堆破烂拿出去
Can somebody get this shit out of here?
两个小时后就开门  动作快点
We open up in two hours. Come on.
把这些钢管擦得亮些
Put some polish on those poles.
一定要闪亮
I want them to shine.
她可以擦擦我的"管子"
She can polish my pole.
有什么问题吗
Is there a problem over here?
没有  女士
No, ma'am.
后边有两箱伏特加
There are two cases of vodka out back.
-把它们搬到吧台来  -我是可以搬
- Bring them to the bar. - You know, I would,
但我不是为你工作的
but I don't work for you.
我是为普罗科特工作的
I work for Mr. Proctor.
你不用给任何人工作了
Now you don't work for anybody.
-收拾东西滚吧  -去你妈的
- Pack your shit and go. - Suck my dick.
送这位先生出去
Please escort this man off the property.
他不该到这里来
He's trespassing.
你要送我离开了
You're gonna escort me now.
遵命
Yes, ma'am.
走吧
Let's go.
好
Okay.
自不量力  贱人
You're out of your league, cunt.
把他带走
Get him out of here.
怎么了
What is it?
有三个费城来的人
There are three men here
要见普罗科特先生
from Philadelphia asking to see Mr. Proctor.
弗拉奇尔的人吗  让他们进来
Frazier's men? Show them in.
先生们
Gentlemen.
你就是雷诺克斯吧
You must be Lennox.
我从我叔叔凯那里听了你不少事
I've heard good things from my Uncle Kai.
请坐
Please, have a seat.
-普罗科特先生呢  -他有别的事
- Where is Mr. Proctor? - Tending to other business.
我会代表他处理事务
I'll be speaking on his behalf.
我们一般只和你老板谈事
We're accustomed to dealing direct with your boss.
我们一般也只和你老板谈事
And we're accustomed to dealing directly with your boss,
也就是弗拉奇尔先生
Mr. Frazier.
鉴于你大老远从费城跑来
But seeing as you drove all the way from Philadelphia,
我这回破个例
I'm willing to make an exception.
你说呢
How about you?
考虑到最近的事  弗拉奇尔先生想要
In light of recent events, Mr. Frazier would like
重新和普罗科特先生建立生意关系
to reestablish his business dealings with Mr. Proctor.
凯奇家族不干了吗
Is the Cage family no longer making deliveries?
为了得到适当的减价
We're prepared to double our previous order
我们准备把订单数量翻倍
in exchange for a modest price reduction.
你想要折扣
You want a discount?
还要普罗科特先生能以个人名义保证
As well as Mr. Proctor's personal assurance
他不再向萨尔瓦多人供货
that he will stop selling to the Salvadorans
协议立刻起效
effective immediately.
普罗科特先生可以继续向弗拉奇尔供货
Mr. Proctor will start selling to Frazier again,
但我们的价格只涨不减
but our prices have gone up, not down,
考虑到最近发生的事
in light of recent events.
涨10%的价
A 10% increase.
至于萨尔瓦多人
And as for the Salvadorans,
回去告诉你老板
tell your boss
凯·普罗科特想给谁供货都行
that Kai Proctor sells to whoever he wants.
谢谢你的接待  保持联系
Thank you for your time. We'll be in touch.
我父亲信奉的神易怒且有报复心
My father believed in an angry and vengeful God,
他会惩罚不忠者  给予他们痛苦和折磨
one who punished transgression with pain and suffering.
我小的时候  父亲让我恐惧
As a child, he taught me to cower in fear.
但随着年纪渐长
But the older I got,
他的固执越来越让我愤怒  所以
the more his dogma angered me, so...
我在背上纹了这个十字来挑战他信奉的神
I put that cross on my back as a challenge to his God.
看看我是不是会遭到他所说的报应
To finally see if I'd be dealt with the way he said I would.
-那你遭到报应了吗  -没有
- And were you? - No.
至少我觉得没有
At least I didn't think so.
但最近我在想  这种惩罚
But lately I've begun to wonder if the punishment
可能更微妙
was something more subtle,
更不易察觉
less obvious.
你很孤独
You're alone.
是啊
Yeah.
你不必这么孤独  我们都不用
You don't have to be. Neither of us does.
我身上有些事你不会喜欢的
You'll learn things about me that you won't like.
我一直住在这里  凯
I've lived in this town my whole life, Kai.
我知道你是什么人
I know who you are.
昨天我们是一种人
We were all someone else yesterday.
明天又会是另一种人
We'll be someone else tomorrow.
你来啦  真是个大惊喜
Hi. This is a nice surprise.
先别这么想
Hold that thought.
米勒老师需要家长签字
Miss Miller wants that signed by a parent.
我刚好在附近  想着你还算是家长
I was in the neighborhood and figured you might still qualify.
最近三次作业你都没交
You didn't hand in your last three assignments.
又或者  我只是漏交了三次作业
Or some might say I'm only three assignments behind.
考虑到我家的情况
Which, given my home circumstances,
我能做到这份上已经很不容易了
is a pretty significant accomplishment,
不是吗
don't you think?
蒂法  你知道我们有什么共同点吗
Deva, you know what you and I have in common?
我们都被骗了16年
We were both lied to for 16 years?
这是其中一点
Yeah, that's one way to look at it.
但还有一点
But there's also this.
我们仍是我们自己
We're the people that we always said we were.
我仍然是你父亲
I'm still your father.
不会变的
That'll never change.
明白吗
Okay?
走吧  我开车送你回家
Come on, I'll drive you home.
不用了  我走回去就好
No, it's okay. I'll walk.
谢谢  爸爸
Thanks, Dad.
-这么准时  -你知道我的  很规律的人
- Right on time. - You know me. I'm a creature of habit.
陪我坐坐
Sit with me.
-我不能  -拜托  店里又没人
- I can't. - Come on, the place is empty.
就五分钟
Five minutes.
我很怀念和你在一起
I miss what we had.
我知道你也很怀念
And I know you miss it, too.
我有说错吗
Am I wrong?
没有
No.
那今晚在老地方见
Then meet me at the motel tonight.
我受宠若惊
I'm flattered.
但我说过要结束一切  我是认真的
But when I said we were through, I meant it.
好吧
Okay.
看来我要继续努力了
I guess I just had to take another run at it.
相信我  我懂的
Believe me, I get it.
-还点往常的吗  -今天算了
- The usual? - Not today.
我刚没了胃口
No, I just lost my appetite.
谢谢咖啡
Thanks for the coffee.
天哪  很抱歉  你没事吧
Oh, my God! I'm so sorry. Are you okay?
只是有点尴尬
Yeah, just a little embarrassed.
那完全是我的错  我应该更小心些的
That was totally my fault. I should be more careful.
我真是笨手笨脚的
Oh, my God. I'm a total spaz.
不  不  不是的
No, no, you're okay.
-祝你愉快  -你也是
- Have a great day. - Yeah, you, too.
-身手不错  -你说什么
- Nice lift. - Excuse me?
那个家伙  他完全不知道被玩了
That guy, he never knew what hit him.
你偷了多少钱
How much you score?
我完全不知道你在说什么
I have no idea what you're talking about.
你担心我是警察吗
What, you worried I'm a cop?
不  我认识镇上所有的警察
No, I know all the cops in this town.
我是担心你是变态
I'm worried you're a creep.
所以你是本地人啦
So you're from around here?
你想干什么
Is there a reason you're still talking to me?
可不是每天都能遇见
Well, it's not every day that I meet a beautiful girl
偷窃技术高超的美女
with mad pickpocket skills.
所以只是想知道你还擅长什么
So just kind of wondering what else you're good at.
我猜也是
I bet you are.
你想去玩玩吗
You want to get out of here?
我和朋友们在办一个派对
I'm throwing a little party with some friends.
绝对有意思
Guaranteed good times.
你真觉得我会和一个陌生人去派对
You actually think I'd go to a party with a total stranger?
我是查理
I'm Charlie.
查理·诺尔斯
Charlie Knowles.
说得好像我应该认识你似的
You say that like I should know who you are.
不  不过我希望你能认识我
No, but I'd like you to.
你真神经
You're crazy.
是的
Yeah.
那你愿意来吗
Does that mean you're coming?
我能带个朋友吗
Can I bring a friend?
人越多越热闹
The more the merrier.
声音呢
And the voice?
不管你听到什么  都别再对我提起
Whatever you hear, I don't want to talk about it.
我很怀念和你在一起
I miss what we had.
我知道你也很怀念
And I know you miss it, too.
-我有说错吗  -没有
- Am I wrong? - No.
真他妈难以置信
Un-fucking-believable.
靠过来
Bring it in.
红骨帮营地在正北三英里处  都是山路
Redbone camp is a three-mile hike due north.
目前情报显示里特斯通在营地里
Current intel shows that Littlestone is in the camp,
所以我们要拿下他
so we are gonna take him down.
日出在六点半
Sunrise is at 0630.
我要嫌疑人在六点三十三分缉拿归案
I want the suspect in custody by 0633.
正北方三里山路
Three-mile hike due north.
突破外围  三个火力小组
Breach the perimeter, three fire teams,
呈标准队形  从这里  这里  还有这里
standard formation, from here, here, and here.
行动迅速  在他们睡觉时袭击
Go in fast, we go in hard while they're sleeping.
要警惕他们反抗
We should still anticipate resistance,
尤其是里特斯通
especially from Littlestone himself.
我们的目标是零伤亡
Now our objective is zero casualties.
就算有人要受伤
But if somebody has to get hit,
那也必须是他们受伤
damn straight it's gonna be one of them.
好了  各位知道规矩
All right, you know the drill.
保持警惕  保住性命
Stay alert, stay alive.
三十分钟后行动
Move out in 30 minutes.
是的  长官
Yes, sir.
你这样坐视不理没问题吗
You okay watching this from the cheap seats?
-你也听到了  这是人家的场子  -弗瑞罗长官
- You heard the man. It's his show. - Commander Ferillo.
我知道你有任务在身
I know that you have a job to do.
我想确保这只是逮捕
I just want to be sure that this is an arrest
不是枪决
and not an execution.
不好意思  你哪位
I'm sorry, who are you?
艾米·金  奇诺警局
Aimee King, Kinaho Police Department.
金警官
Well, Officer King,
那个警察杀手得跟我走
that cop killer is coming home with me.
要死要活  就看他了
Dead or alive, the choice is his.
你再好好考虑站在哪一边
You might want to consider whose side you're on.
-长官  -金  够了
- Commander-- - King, that's enough.
听起来你在帮那个人渣说话
Sounded like you were sticking up for that piece of shit.
你我都知道
You and I both know that
切顿没法活着离开这座山
Chayton isn't leaving this mountain alive.
知道  但我不在乎
Yeah, but I don't have a problem with that.
你为什么在乎
So why do you?
我也认识西沃恩
Look, I knew Siobhan, too.
他像扭树枝一样扭断了她的脖子
He snapped her neck like a twig.
还很享受
And he enjoyed it.
这是哪里啊
What is this place?
本来是我父母的房子
It was my parents' house.
他们死后就成了我的
And then after they died, it became mine.
-不错  -现在什么样我说了算
- Cool. - Now it's anything I want it to be.
听起来很棒啊
Sounds awesome.
来吧  我带你们转转
Come on. I'll show you around.
你们全都住在这里吗
You guys all live here together?
我们跟别的家庭一样
Well, we're just like any other family
只不过我们真的会照顾彼此
except we actually take care of each other.
你想见见他们吗
You want to meet 'em?
-好啊  -来
- Sure. - Come on.
蒂法  这里很吓人啊
Deva, this place freaks me out.
-来啊  会很好玩的  -我们不属于这里
- Come on, it'll be fun. - We don't belong here.
你要想走就走  我要留在这
If you want to go, go. I'm staying.
好啦  大伙  这位是蒂法
All right, everybody, this is Deva.
那一位是  你叫什么
And that's-- what's your name?
-比蒂  -比蒂
- Beaty. - Beaty.
-好了  给你  -谢谢
- All right, here you go. - Thank you.
他在等你
He's waiting for you.
-叔叔  你找我  -是
- You wanted to see me, Uncle? - Yeah.
费城来的朋友告诉我  你不太明白
Our friend from Philadelphia tells me you were a little confused
之前弗拉奇尔先生叫他转达的提议
about the offer he delivered from Mr. Frazier earlier today.
那不是提议  那是侮辱
It wasn't an offer. It was an insult.
这是修复大家长期以来
It was a first step in repairing a long-standing
非常重要的商业关系的第一步
and very important business relationship.
他们从我们的竞争对手那里买货
They were buying from our competition
而你要用降价来奖励他们
and you want to reward that with a discount?
他们是顾客  我想要赢回他们的生意
They're the customer. I want to earn their business back.
小小的让步为了辉煌的明天
A small concession towards a bigger future.
但那不是我们商量好的
But that's not what we agreed upon.
我已经同意了弗拉奇尔的条件
I already agreed to Frazier's terms.
我们会降低单价
We will reduce the unit price,
即刻停止所有对萨尔瓦多人的销售
stop all sales to the Salvadorans immediately.
明白吗
Is that understood?
叔叔
Uncle.
想清楚啊
听明白了吗  丽贝卡
Is that understood, Rebecca?
-明白  -很好
- Yes. - Good.
我叫你来  是觉得你会想要向雷诺克斯先生
Now, I called you in because I'm sure you'd like to apologize
及他的同事们道个歉
to Mr. Lennox and his associates for the misunderstanding.
对这个误会我深表歉意
I apologize for the misunderstanding.
下次不会了
It won't happen again.
很好  谢谢  丽贝卡  你可以走了
Good. Thank you, Rebecca. You can go now.
普罗科特先生  谢谢
Thank you, Mr. Proctor.
滚出去
Get out.
都他妈的滚出去
Get the fuck out!
没人要的婊子
如果你朝我开枪了  混蛋
If you shoot me, motherfucker,
就什么生日礼物也别想拿
you ain't getting shit for your birthday.
你迟到了
You're late.
我先说清楚
Now let me be clear.
我相信干掉切顿那个混蛋
I'm trusting that taking out this Chayton motherfucker
你就能专心做事了
will get you focused on the real work at hand.
-切顿在哪  -去你的
- Where's Chayton? - Fuck you.
他在哪
Where is he?
进去
Move in.
-前进前进  -行动
- Go, go. - Move!
警长在哪
Where's the sheriff?
-冲进去  快  -是联邦调查局
- Move in! Now! - FBI!
赶快离开这
Get the fuck out of here!
跪下  给我跪下
Get on the ground! Get on the ground!
跪下
Down!
快  跪下
Go! Down now!
给我跪下
Get on the ground!
联邦调查局  跪下
FBI, get on the ground!
-跪下  跪下  -我们是联邦调查局
- Get on the ground! Get on the ground! - FBI!
跪下
Get down!
别给我乱动
Sit still, I said!
别动  切顿
Don't move, Chayton!
我不会再让他们抓我进监狱了  艾米
I'm not gonna let them put me in another cage, Aimee.
-你杀了警察  -那不是杀害
- You murdered a cop. - It's not murder.
是场战争
It's war.
我认识她  切顿  她不该死的
I knew her, Chayton. She didn't deserve to die.
她选择了当警察就要做好觉悟
She chose her fate when she put on that uniform.
别过来
Stop!
你不会朝我开枪的
You're not gonna shoot me.
必要时我会开的
I will if I have to.
不  你不会的
No, you won't.
你为什么不朝他开枪
Why the fuck didn't you shoot him, huh?
他去哪了
Where is he?
我他妈问你他去哪了
I said where the fuck is he?
别这么做  长官
You don't want to do that, sir.
你要为此负责  混蛋
I'll have your badge for this, fucker.
先排队吧你
Get in fucking line.
天呐  我的天  这也太猛了
Oh, man. Oh, my God, that was strong.
但很美妙  这是你的第一次
That was amazing. That was your first one.
做得很好  吸得很好
It was good. It was a good pull.
现在来喝酒是不是有点早
Is it too early for a drink?
要看在哪喝了
That depends on who you ask.
把瓶子给我吧
Just leave the bottle.
谢谢你能来参加葬礼
Thank you for coming to the funeral.
对于尊敬你的人
Someone shows you respect in life,
你能做的就是在葬礼上好好悼念他们
the least you can do is return the favor when they're gone.
我为你感到难过
I'm sorry for your loss.
像我这样的人
You know, men like me...
常常徘徊在鬼门关
we're no strangers to death.
或许因为此  当死亡来临时
Maybe because of that, when it hits close to home,
我们会觉得有责任
we feel responsible.
或许你就是责任感强
Well, maybe you are responsible.
是  我也这么想
Yeah, I suppose so.
你没事吧
You okay?
有点累
Tired.
来睡吧
Come to bed.
你要走吗
You heading out?
是的
Yeah.
告诉我
So tell me,
你在追查什么东西  还是被追查了
are you chasing something or are you being chased?
-通常来说  -两方面都有吧
- Can usually tell... - A little bit of both.
不管怎么样  希望你别再困扰
Well, either way, I hope it works out for you.
谢谢
Thanks.
谢谢你
Thank you.
-嗨  -嗨
- Hey. - Hey, yourself.